{"entrance":{"x":1,"y":1},"exit":{"x":4,"y":18},"grid":[[{"x":0,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":0,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":1,"door":true,"axis":"y","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":4,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":5,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":6,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":1,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":1,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":4,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":5,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":6,"y":2,"door":true,"axis":"y","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_03","left":"doors_1_03","back":"doors_1_03","right":"doors_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"key":"yellow"},{"x":7,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":2,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_04","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":2,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":4,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":5,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":6,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"doors_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"doors_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":3,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":3,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":4,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":5,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":6,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":4,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":4,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":5,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_02","left":"doors_1_02","back":"doors_1_02","right":"doors_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":5,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":7,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":8,"y":6,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":9,"y":6,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":7,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":8,"y":7,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_04"}},{"x":9,"y":7,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":7,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":8,"y":8,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_03","top":"ceilings_1_03"}},{"x":9,"y":8,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":9,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_02"}},{"x":5,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":9,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_05","left":"doors_1_05","back":"doors_1_05","right":"doors_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"},"key":"red"},{"x":8,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":9,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_05","left":"walls_1_05","back":"walls_1_05","right":"walls_1_05","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":10,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":10,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_02"}},{"x":3,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":11,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":11,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":12,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":12,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_02","left":"walls_1_02","back":"walls_1_02","right":"walls_1_02","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":13,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":13,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":14,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":14,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_07","left":"walls_1_07","back":"walls_1_07","right":"walls_1_07","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_06","left":"walls_1_06","back":"walls_1_06","right":"walls_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_02"}},{"x":4,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_09","left":"walls_1_09","back":"walls_1_09","right":"walls_1_09","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":15,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":15,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_03","left":"walls_1_03","back":"walls_1_03","right":"walls_1_03","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":16,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":16,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":17,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_06","left":"doors_1_06","back":"doors_1_06","right":"doors_1_06","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"doors_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"doors_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_04","left":"walls_1_04","back":"walls_1_04","right":"walls_1_04","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":17,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":18,"blocking":false,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":18,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}],[{"x":0,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":1,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":2,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":3,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":4,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":5,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_08","left":"walls_1_08","back":"walls_1_08","right":"walls_1_08","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":6,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":7,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":8,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}},{"x":9,"y":19,"blocking":true,"sides":{"front":"walls_1_01","left":"walls_1_01","back":"walls_1_01","right":"walls_1_01","bottom":"floors_1_01","top":"ceilings_1_01"}}]],"obstacles":[{"x":5,"y":1,"name":"static_objects_1_02","blocking":true,"width":0.375,"length":0.375,"height":0.453125},{"x":4,"y":2,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":8,"y":2,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":5,"y":3,"name":"static_objects_1_05","blocking":true,"width":0.3125,"length":0.3125,"height":0.796875},{"x":3,"y":4,"name":"static_objects_1_01","blocking":true,"width":0.328125,"length":0.328125,"height":1},{"x":5,"y":4,"name":"static_objects_1_01","blocking":true,"width":0.328125,"length":0.328125,"height":1},{"x":8,"y":6,"name":"static_objects_1_04","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.640625},{"x":4,"y":7,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":8,"y":8,"name":"static_objects_1_04","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.640625},{"x":4,"y":9,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":1,"y":11,"name":"static_objects_1_06","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.5625},{"x":8,"y":11,"name":"blue_torch","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.1875,"length":0.1875,"height":0.546875},{"x":4,"y":12,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125},{"x":1,"y":14,"name":"static_objects_1_06","blocking":true,"width":0.234375,"length":0.234375,"height":0.5625},{"x":8,"y":14,"name":"blue_torch","blocking":true,"animated":true,"width":0.1875,"length":0.1875,"height":0.546875},{"x":4,"y":15,"name":"static_objects_1_03","blocking":false,"width":0.203125,"length":0.203125,"height":0.125}],"items":[{"color":"yellow","type":"keyitem","x":4,"y":1,"name":"items_02"},{"color":"blue","type":"keyitem","x":8,"y":3,"name":"items_01"},{"amount":50,"type":"healthitem","x":7,"y":6,"name":"items_12"},{"amount":25,"type":"healthitem","x":4,"y":9,"name":"items_04"},{"color":"red","type":"keyitem","x":1,"y":10,"name":"items_03"},{"amount":10,"type":"healthitem","x":1,"y":12,"name":"items_05"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"chaingun","x":8,"y":12,"name":"items_09"},{"amount":15,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"pistol","x":1,"y":15,"name":"items_08"},{"amount":50,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"chaingun","x":1,"y":16,"name":"items_06"},{"amount":20,"type":"ammoitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":2,"y":16,"name":"items_07"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"shotgun","x":7,"y":16,"name":"items_10"}],"enemies":[{"x":4,"y":12,"name":"imp","type":"imp","width":0.5,"length":0.5,"height":0.625}]}